[{"answer": "my friend, why do you have to   Hello, my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Take what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "So that's here", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't wanna be that place", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hey.  Oh, is that a label maker", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Love the Label Baby, baby.  You know those things make great gifts, I just got one of those for my friend for Christmas", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "One my friend! my friend.  No, my my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Oh, you know, like when someone opens something up and they go,", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Why'd you get him a gift anyway", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I love it!  This is fantastic!  Look at this couch, is this velvet?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "A fan?  I would drape myself in velvet if it were socially acceptable. And look at this, hardwood floors", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I'm sure I will. my friend and my friend are at the coffee shop", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes.  A male roommate", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Exactly!  You know how they get animals to reproduce in captivity? They just put them in the same cage", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Oh, that's the worst part of it.  He looks just like me", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Oh, that's the worst part of it.  He looks just like me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I look like me and I'm working from the outside.  Who do you think is in the better position", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Are you through", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "The wedding is off?  What happened", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I can't call my friend and ask for the tickets back", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Are you even vaguely familiar with the concept of giving?  There's no grace period", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, if he can regift, why can't you degift", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I have a point, I have a point", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Thank Scott.  He recommended it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes he is", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, this is my building", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "This was fun, you know", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Aren't you gonna invite me upstairs", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I would love to go upstairs", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend's his mailman", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Who goes", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hey.  What are you doing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "My door", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Don't worry, my friend.  I didn't come by to yell at you, I didn't come by for that at all.  I just came by to pick up my label maker. I gave you a label maker and now I would like to have it back", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "But you gave me a ticket to the Super Bowl.  Hand it over, my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Here's the TV.  I know you wanted to watch the Super Bowl.  Do you at least have some towels we could sit on?  It's, like, a four hour game", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Label-Maker.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "How am I gonna get out of this?  Think my friend, think", "qsentId": 38}]